Mobile: +852 95227391 | Email: ifiddle@gmail.com

YUKI PUN

PERSONAL PARTICULARS

Full Name : PUN Siu Yee Latest Position : Senior Graphic Designer (Game UI and UX)

Gender: Female Work Experience: 15+ years

Date of Birth: 27th March 1982 Nationality: Hong Kong

Availability: End of Oct 2017

SUMMARY

Over fifteen years working experience in graphic, game, web and multimedia field. Finish RWD web project independently from design to programming. Solid game graphic and UI experience from PC to Java to symbian to smartphone. Good at drawing either in Japanese comic style or western realistic style, hand nor computer.

- Good team player
- Able to finish works independently
- Initiative, willing to learn, efficiency and responsibility

Some of my artworks are available in my online portfolio web: http://pofo.i-fiddle.net.

EDUCATION LANGUAGE

2014-2015 BSc(Hons) in Multimedia Computing (Upper 2nd)

Coventry University UK

■ Usability ■ Web with API ■ 3D Animation ■ Movie Making ■ iPhone Development ■ Pervasive Computing ■ Algorithms and Data Structures

■ Individual Project (Unity Game)

2014 Certificate in Algorithms and Data Structures (Bridging Course)

PEAK

2005-2008 High Certificate in Visual Communication (Credit)

HK IVE (Sha Tin)

2003-2005 Certificate in Multimedia & Internet Technology

HK IVE (Tsing Yi)

1994-1999 Form 5 Graduate - Chi(D), Eng Syl.B(E), Maths(C)

Kit Sam Secondary School

Spoken

Cantonese (Fluent)

English (Good)

Mandarin (Fair)

Written

Chinese (Fluent)

English (Fair)

WORK EXPERIENCE SKILL

Senior Graphic Designer Aug 2014 - Present Smart City Tech. Ltd.

Responsible for UI/UX design, game art, promotional materials and website develop in mobile game "Heroes Flick", hand on experience with game engine Unity3D. Finished website including www.heroesflick.com and www.aurumpacific.com.hk, from draft to server side.

Senior Graphic Designer Mar 2014 - Aug 2014 Mooff Games Ltd..

Responsible for mobile game project "不是足球遊戲" UI/UX design and game graphic illustration, hand on experience with CocosBuilder and Spine.

Ul Graphic Designer Oct 2013 - Mar 2014 Ucan Commercial Ltd.

Responsible for mobile game project "超級無敵獎門人終極篇" UI/UX design and game graphic illustration, hand on experience with CocosBuilder.

Graphic Designer Jan 2013 - Sep 2013 iGPSD Ltd.

Responsible for iphone/ipad/Android apps graphic design and all kinds of design works, web development for mobile & desktop. (eg: www.ecqapp.com/new/index.php)

Office Administrator Jul 2011 - May 2012 So Kee Company (Ireland)

The job during my working holiday in Ireland, being as an office administrator at chinese supermarket sale office, job duties included documentation work, CS, stock management and take wholesale orders by phone in Mandarin / English / Cantonese.

Senior Graphic Designer Sep 2008 - May 2011 Monarch Floral Decoration Co. Ltd.

Responsible for event design projects included wedding decoration and commercial exhibition booth, all kinds of in-house design and promotional materials. Guide junior designer to finish design job.

Multimedia Designer Sep 2007 - Apr 2008 TG Media Corporations Ltd.

Responsible for web design projects, and all kinds of in house design and promotional materials.

Graphic Designer Jul 2006 - Aug 2007 MG Soft Ltd. / MGIE Ltd.

Responsible for mobile game graphics, pixel art, and all kinds of company promotional materials, such as leaflet, poster, website design...etc. Involved game project include 超級麻雀俱樂部, client project for Towngas and Nissin.

Graphic Designer Sep 2004 - Jul 2006 Funmobile Ltd.

Responsible to create JAVA mobile game graphics independently, start from concept art, storyboard drawing, character design, interface design, pixel art, animation ...etc . Involved game project include Doki Dogstar Cards, Doki Pipe Wonderland.

Graphic Designer Feb 2004 - Sep 2004 Jijo Collect Kid's Wear Whsle. Co. Ltd.

Responsible for Illustrate and design print-art of kidswear, including copyright art of brand Popeye®, Olive $Oyl^{\mathbb{M}}$ and Betty $Boop^{\mathbb{M}}$, and produce graphic materials for (Leaflet, name-card...etc).

PC Game 2D Artist Jun 2001 - Jul 2002 Info-Mission Tech. Inc. Ltd.

Responsible for PC game UI design and game graphic illustration, involved game project include 少林足球, 超人光之傳承.

Graphic

- Pixel Art
- Hand Drawing
- Digital Illustration
- Comic style
- Realistic style

Design

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Dreamweaver
- Flash

Web

- ♦ HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- ❖ MySQL
- Javascript
- Jquery
- AJAX
- ❖ ActionScript
- RWD Web
- Bootstrap
- Thinkphp

Game Dev

- Unity3D
- Cocos2d
- Spine
- ❖ Git / SVN

Video

- 3ds Max
- Premiere
- After Effect